

Athena Davis

Energetic Python Django Developer with 5 Years of Experience in Python Django Website Development

Senior python Django Manager with five years of experience. Initiated project plans and raised new solutions for 20+ clients. Aiming to find a Django developer position to improve the efficacy and efficiency of python team members at BXDY Company.

(305)-998-0987

Miami, USA

athenast@gmail.com

SKILLS

Detailed Minded

Project Execution

Database Management

Search Engine Optimization

Sensitive to Numerical Data

Core Python Expertise Deep Learning

Strong r rocessing skins

Strong Processing Skills Team Player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python Django Manager

KKRE Corp.

2018 - Present

• Led a team of three to conduct medium-scale projects

• Enhanced the productivity of the Python Developer section by improving the work distribution and process

Python Developer

JJJA Corp.

2016 - 2018

- Structured 4+ skeleton websites per month for senior employees to further expand and decorate
- Engaged in weekly project meetings and proposed imaginative solutions

EDUCATION



University of Illinois Urbana - Champaign

2012 - 2016

B.S. in Computer Science

GPA: 3.53 / 4.0

Graduated with Honors